pixtastock.com 2017-08-30

# Privacy Policy - Stock Photos PIXTA

We, PIXTA Inc. (hereinafter referred to as “Pixta” or “we”) handle with the utmost attention, and take strict measures to protect, the personal information collected from each user (hereinafter referred to as the “User”) of our service “PIXTA” (hereinafter referred to as the “Service”) in accordance with the following Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as the “Privacy Policy”).

## Definition of Personal Information

In this Privacy Policy, the “Personal Information” shall mean information about a living individual which can identify the specific individual by name, date of birth or other description contained in such information (including such information as will allow easy reference to other information and will thereby enable the identification of the specific individual), such as e-mail address, password, name, date of birth, postal address, telephone number, and credit card information collected from the User for the use of the Service.   
We may also collect information concerning the User’s usage situation on the Service including but not limited to, information of IP address, Cookies, and browser. However, we do not regard that information as included in the Personal Information because it alone cannot identify the specific individual; provided, however, that it shall be regarded as the Personal Information if it is combined and used together with any of the Personal Information.   
We do not intend to require or collect the Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18 years, with knowing the age of such person. People who are younger than 18 years old may not use the Service. 

## Use of Personal Information

We will use the Personal Information that has been registered by the User in accordance with this Privacy Policy for the purposes of: 

  1. Provision of the Service;
  2. Provision of customer services including but not limited to handling inquiries or claims;
  3. Maintenance of the system and fixing problems;
  4. Confirmation of the User’s identification;
  5. Charging for the purchase price and payment of the compensation;
  6. Displaying on Pixta’s website accessed by the User or on the User’s other mobile devices, sending by e-mail or by mail, or providing by telephone or any other communication devices, of any information regarding Pixta’s other available services or our affiliated companies’ goods or services, which is considered to be beneficial to each User; provided, however, that the User is able to cease or resume such use of the Personal Information by notifying thereof to us;
  7. Sending e-mails to obtain the User’s consent for the use of his or her Personal Information;
  8. Creation of statistical material that has been processed to make the User’s identification unidentifiable or unrecognizable (hereinafter referred to as the “Statistical Material”) by aggregating and analyzing attributes of the User’s Personal Information, and use of the Statistical Material for our business operation including but not limited to development for the new services;
  9. Handling of such relevant matters as stipulated in terms or rules of the Service;
  10. Other purposes related to the above purposes.

## Handling of Personal Information

Respecting the User’s privacy, we acknowledge that the Personal Information is important to be protected and we take the strict measures to control the User’s Personal Information. We will take the necessary preventive measures against the risk of unauthorized access, falsification, leak, loss or destruction in relation to the User’s Personal Information, and in the event of occurrence of any of the foregoing, we will promptly handle it in order to minimize trouble to each User.

## Disclosure and Entrustment etc. of Personal Information

We shall not disclose or entrust the User’s Personal Information to any third party, without having first informed the User of information regarding to whom and for what purpose his or her Personal Information will be disclosed or entrusted, and obtained the User’s consent thereto (Instead of obtaining the User’s consent, we may post on screen clear explanation thereof and provide the User with a chance to refuse such entrustment); provided, however, that we may disclose or entrust the Personal Information in the following cases:

  1. When we entrust the User’s Personal Information to any subcontractor(s) to the extent necessary for the purposes of the use of the Personal Information set forth in this Privacy Policy;
  2. When we entrust the User’s Personal Information to any company or companies such as subcontractor(s) with which we have executed Non-Disclosure Agreement in advance to the extent necessary;
  3. When the User violates the Terms of Use of each of our services, our policies or notices, or it is considered to be necessary to protect rights or property of any other User, third party, or Pixta;
  4. When we are legally requested to disclose the User’s Personal Information by the courts, governmental order, the Police or any other public body with similar legal status;
  5. When disclosure of the User’s Personal Information is urgently necessary to safeguard the User’s life, physical health or property; or
  6. When disclosure or entrustment of the User’s Personal Information is permitted pursuant to laws and regulations or provisions of the Terms of Use etc. that the User has agreed to.

## Use of Cookies

Within the Service, Cookies may be used upon actions such as “collecting the access history”,“confirming Login status”, “saving cart information”, and “changing order of results” etc. The use of Cookies is intended to improve conveniences in the User’s use of the Service, and it does not recognize any of the User’s name or telephone number etc. Any User who desires invalidation of Cookies may invalidate by changing the configuration of web browser. The User who declines the use of Cookies may still be able to continue limited use of the Service such as viewing websites, but unable to use services using Cookies as above mentioned.  
Also the Service uses Cookies and Web beacons issued from advertising system which has been contracted or adopted for access analysis or advertising distribution, but they do not identify any individual.  
Behavioral Targeting Advertisement Services listed on “Behavioral Targeting Advertisement the Services List” may be used in a part of the Service in order to distribute proper advertisements to each User. Behavioral Targeting Advertisement is an advertising method to distribute selected advertisements in accordance with interests or preference of each User who accesses to the Service on the basis of the browsing record information etc. Any User who wants to refuse such Behavioral Targeting Advertisements has to access the opt-out pages of each of the companies listed on Behavioral Targeting Advertisement the Services List, and conduct invalidation procedures.  
“Behavioral Targeting Advertisement the Services List” is here. 

## Alteration, Deletion or Disclosure of Personal Information

If any of the User desires confirmation of or alteration to his or her Personal Information that has been registered with us, the User shall take the confirmation or alteration procedures designated by Pixta. 

## Retention Period and Period of Use of Personal Information

Even after the User has stopped using the Service, we may retain the Personal Information for an unspecified period of time.

## SSL

In order to protect the User’s Personal Information, Pixta’s website accommodates SSL as appropriate. Through the browsers with security features compatible such as Microsoft Internet Explorer, the Personal Information entered by the User will be transmitted after having been automatically encrypted.  
Any User who uses a browser that is not compatible with SSL may not be able to access to Pixta’s website or enter any information. 

## Management of Personal Information

Any and all the Personal Information that has been registered with us will be controlled by Pixta and Pixta’s subcontractor(s) that has executed proper Non-Disclosure Agreement with Pixta. We will take protection measures against any unauthorized access to the network operated by Pixta, and will take the efforts to prevent any access to our server from outside of our network. We take the appropriate measures and control policies upon transmission of any specific Personal Information in order to keep the security of the User’s Personal Information and maintain the accuracy thereof.

## Trouble Relating to Personal Information

We will use the User’s registered e-mail address and password in order to confirm the User’s identity. Each User shall be responsible for safekeeping of such password and we shall not be liable for any trouble arising out of or caused by registered e-mail address or password leaked due to the User’s negligence. We will take the utmost efforts for protection of the User’s Personal Information. However, we shall not be liable to any trouble caused by the User’s negligence or to any problem caused by trouble occurring in the course of the User’s using internet.

## Joint Use of Personal Information 

Your Personal Information may be jointly used with our group companies. Please read the “Joint Use of Personal Information in our Group” for the details of such joint use. 

## Other Important Points

We shall have the right to revise or change provisions of this Privacy Policy, at any time, at our sole discretion. In the case of any material change in this Privacy Policy or usage of the Personal Information by Pixta, we will either post a notice on the Service or send an e-mail to the User in order to notify of such change. The provisions of this Privacy Policy shall take effect between the User and Pixta, and will not apply to any third party including but not limited to the parties being linked from the Service. We shall not be liable to the User’s Personal Information that is registered or handled in any outside website linked from the Service because it is not covered by or subject to this Privacy Policy under Pixta’s control.  
The number of companies constituting our group or the name(s) thereof may be changed due to any reason such as reorganization. 

## Claims or Inquiries regarding Personal Information

Please click here if you have any question regarding this Privacy Policy.

As of September 1, 2015  
2020 (c) PIXTA Inc. All Rights ReservedPIXTA Inc.

### Joint Use of Personal Information in our Group

In order to provide you with better service, we will jointly use your Personal Information with our group companies within the following scopes when it is necessary. We will make the utmost efforts for strict management with our group in jointly using your Personal Information.   
We may amend this policy of joint use whenever necessary for the future. In such case, we will notify you or publicly announce for your attention. 

  1. Items that may be used jointly:  
Name, Postal Address, Telephone Number, E-mail Address, Date of Birth, Gender and Other Personal Information collected. 
  2. Scope of joint users:  
  3. Scope of use: 
    1. Provision of the Service;
    2. Provision of customer services including but not limited to handling inquiries or claims;
    3. Maintenance of the system and fixing problems;
    4. Confirmation of the User’s identification; 
    5. Charging for the purchase price and payment of the compensation;
    6. Displaying on Pixta’s website accessed by the User or on the User’s other mobile devices, sending by e-mail or by mail, or providing by telephone or any other communication devices, of any information regarding Pixta’s other available services or our affiliated companies’ goods or services, which is considered to be beneficial to each User; provided, however, that the User is able to cease or resume such use of the Personal Information by notifying thereof to us;
    7. Sending e-mails to obtain the User’s consent for the use of his or her Personal Information;
    8. Creation of statistical material that has been processed to make the User’s identification unidentifiable or unrecognizable (hereinafter referred to as the “Statistical Material”) by aggregating and analyzing attributes of the User’s Personal Information, and use of the Statistical Material for our business operation including but not limited to development for the new services;
    9. Handling of such relevant matters as stipulated in terms or rules of the Service;
    10. Other purposes related to the above purposes.
  4. Entity responsible for management of joint use:  
PIXTA Inc.
